So Joe, we're going to build this earthquake app, but
Joe 我们要构建一个与地震相关的应用
where should we start?
但应该从哪里入手呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, every great app starts with having a clear vision for
— 所有优秀的应用在开始的时候都具有明确的
its existence, right?
设计意图 对吗？
In this case, we'd like to enable users like you
对于我们而言 目的是让像你一样的用户
to get a better sense of the seismic activity near them, or around the world.
能够更好地获取身边或全世界有关地震活动的资讯
&gt;&gt; Cool.
— 不错
&gt;&gt; But our idea for an app could be many other things, like a meme creator, or
— 应用创意可以非常丰富 例如 迷因创建应用
a restaurant finder, or even a task management app.
餐馆发现应用 甚至任务管理应用
At the end of the day, it should be something that adds value and
但应用始终应能为用户提供价值
is a joy to use.
让用户乐于使用
Otherwise, why distribute it?
不然 为什么大家都要用呢？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, absolutely.
— 是的 没错
So I guess we should get really crisp on what kind of information
所以 我们应认真考虑要显示
we want to show and what kind of controls we want to give to the user.
哪些信息 为用户提供哪些控制功能
&gt;&gt; Yes, indeed.
— 是的 没错
In app-speak, we call this designing a killer user experience.
在应用领域 我们将此称为设计优质的用户体验
&gt;&gt; I had some ideas too.
— 我也有一些想法
Do you want to see some sketches?
想看看我画的草图吗？
&gt;&gt; Absolutely, nice work on the napkins by the way.
— 当然 顺便说一句 在纸巾上作画不错哦
Super scrappy.
凌乱的美
&gt;&gt; Yeah, you know how it is.
— 是的 你懂的 就是这个感觉
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
— 嗯
&gt;&gt; It's a pretty simple idea, actually.
— 其实我的想法挺简单
We display a list of earthquakes and we highlight the magnitude of each one, and
要显示地震列表 并突出显示每次地震的震级
we share some important information about where and when it occurred.
再共享一些重要信息 例如地震发生的地点和时间
&gt;&gt; Very cool, I love it.
— 非常好 我喜欢
Giving prominence to the magnitude here makes sense and you got location and
在这里突出显示震级很不错 还有地点
date and time.
日期和时间
It'd also be a great idea to sort the results by maybe magnitude or recency.
如果把结果按照震级或距离远近排列也不错
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
— 同意
&gt;&gt; Or how about allowing the user to focus in certain locations around
— 让用户能够重点关注世界上的某个地点
the world?
怎么样？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, exactly.
— 是的 没错
Okay cool, so, where can we find a reliable source of earthquake data?
非常好 那么 我们应该从哪里找到可靠的地震数据源呢？
&gt;&gt; We can just grab data from the Internet.
— 只需要捕捉网上的数据就行了
&gt;&gt; Okay, but when I Google search, all I'm getting are a bunch of websites.
— 好的 但当我在 Google 上搜索时 只能得到一些网站
How can I use that in an app?
这该如何在应用中加以利用呢？
&gt;&gt; Let's modify that search a little bit.
— 我们来对搜索内容进行一些修改
&gt;&gt; Okay.
— 嗯
&gt;&gt; You'll want to add web API in there.
— 里面应该加上 “Web API”
&gt;&gt; API, what's that?
— API 是什么？
&gt;&gt; API is just short hand for Application Programming Interface.
— API 是应用程序编程接口的缩写
It's how a software product or service makes certain parts of its functionality
软件产品或服务利用 API 将自身的某些特定功能
or data available to use in other software.
或数据 提供给其他软件使用
It's the app's way of saying, if you want to build something new using
应用以这种方式告诉对方 如果想要使用我们的某些数据或功能
some of our data or functionality, here's how we can work together.
来构建新创意 可以按照怎样的方式开展合作
&gt;&gt; Cool, it sounds really powerful.
— 不错 感觉 API 功能很强大啊
&gt;&gt; Yes it is, totally.
— 嗯 的确如此
It's like a programmatic partnership that when done well,
它是一种编程合作关系 如果很好地加以利用
can create some serious value, even impact the world.
可以创造极大的价值 甚至影响世界
When you see apps posting to Twitter or Facebook or
当你看到各种各样的应用时 无论是在 Twitter 或 Facebook 上发布信息
displaying housing prices on a Google map or
在 Google 地图上展示房价
live streaming video, taking credit card payments to an online store,
流媒体视频直播、在线商店、信用卡支付
even mustering users to aid in disaster relief, they're all probably using APIs.
甚至召集用户支援灾区 这些应用很可能都会用到 API
And the possibilities and
其具有的潜能
problems that can be solved with them seem to be endless.
是无限的 使用它们可以解决的问题也数不胜数
&gt;&gt; Okay Joe, I don't know.
— 嗯 Joe
I'm pretty pumped, but in our case, we're looking for an API that can
听得我都激动起来了 但对于我们来讲 我们要找的是
integrate information about earthquakes from the Internet into our app.
能够将网上地震相关信息集成到应用当中的 API
&gt;&gt; Yup, exactly.
— 是的 没错
But the process we'll be following can be used for all kinds of app ideas.
但我们所遵从的这一过程对所有的应用创意都适用
&gt;&gt; Hey, Joe, check this out.
— Joe 来看看
I think I found just the one.
我好像找到了
For this quiz,
在此测验中
what are some possible places to find earthquake data on the Internet?
在网上哪里能找到地震相关的数据呢？
Do a search, and find at least two websites, and
搜索一下 至少找出两个网站
put them in the field here.
将网址填入此处空白